It's that kind of misery, the kind where
you were nice to me but only [music] in
the evening. So, I ask him, am I just
dreaming? I love you [singing] so much
that it's dripping, dripping [music]
from my heart. And so, I'm sorry. I know
I'm too much to love, to trust. I'm
nothing but [music] a mess. It's that
kind of misery, the kind where you were
nice to me but [music] only in the
evening. So, I ask him, am I just
dreaming? You're what I give a living
since I have nobody else. I keep [music]
screaming, I keep breathing in the
living like it helps.
It's a misery cuz you get told me always
that you care. And I know it's true yet
you need [music] to get me out your
hair. It's a
living that you told me why can't you
choose me? The greatest [music]
and last of fairy tales is what you
seek. It's